Anita Riggio Papers
© 2008 University of Connecticut
Anita Riggio Papers.
undated, 1968-2000.
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center.
Riggio, Anita.
17 linear feet.
Anita Riggio has illustrated a number of children's books and has also worked as a cartoonist and a commercial illustrator. The collection consists of original artwork and manuscripts for 25 children's books and two magazine articles, in addition to a selection of Ms. Riggio's production materials for her commercial work.
MSS19970121
Biography
Anita Riggio has illustrated a number of children's books and has also worked as a cartoonist and a commercial illustrator. A native of Clifton, New Jersey, she was the middle child in a family of seven, with one brother, three sisters, and two parents. Ms. Riggio attended the local parochial school and spent holidays planning shows for her large extended Italian-American family. She attended Lacordaire School in Upper Montclair, NJ, and worked as an illustrator for The Hartford Courant in Hartford, CT. Ms. Riggio is currently on faculty in the MFA in Creative Writing program at Lesley University in Boston, MA. She adapted her 1994 work Beware the Brindlebeast for the National Theatre of the Deaf's Little Theatre of the Deaf 2007-2008 tour. She lives in Wethersfield, CT, with her husband Roland Axelson.
Scope and Content
The collection consists of original artwork and manuscripts for 25 children's books and two magazine articles, in addition to a selection of Ms. Riggio's production materials for her commercial work. Some artwork from her days as a student are included in series III.
Arrangement
Series I: Children's Literature and Illustration ( undated, 1981-1994 ) contains artwork and manuscript material for 25 children's books and two magazine articles. The series contains Subseries A: Unpublished works (undated, 1981-1986) and Subseries B: Published works (1987-1994).
Series II: Commercial Art and Graphic Design ( undated, 1982-1989 ) contains artwork and production material for works of commercial art and graphic design, including posters, stationery, newspaper illustrations, and magnets.
Series III: Personal and Family Art ( undated, 1968-2000 ) includes sketchpads from Riggio's early education as an artist, as well as unidentified drawings and paintings produced for personal use.
Series IV: Ephemera ( 1980-1996 )contains fanmail and newspaper articles about Riggio's career.
Related Material
Archives & Special Collections has a substantial collection of materials pertaining to children's literature and associated artwork. For detailed information on these collections please contact the curator or ask at the reference desk.
Separated Material
The following materials have been separated from the collection and cataloged:
Author/Illustrator
Beware the Brindlebeast, Boyds Mills, 1994. CLC C904
Gert and Frieda, Atheneum, 1990. CLC B84, Levy E2988
Secret signs: along the Underground Railroad, Boyds Mills, 1997. CLC D778
Smack dab in the middle! Putnam's, 2002. CLC D776
Wake up, William! Atheneum, 1987. Levy B1165, CLC C44
Illustrator
Coal Mine Peaches, by Michelle Dionetti, Orchard Books, 1991. Levy F1497
I eat dinner, by Margery Facklam, Little, Brown, 1987. CLC A4298
I go to sleep, by Margery Facklam, Little, Brown, 1987. CLC A4299
Jumping Jenny, by Bonnie Pryor, Morrow Junior Books, 1992. CLC B303
Whispering cloth, by Pegi Dietz Shea, stitched by You Yang, Boyds Mills, 1995. CLC D472
Index Terms
This record series is indexed under the following controlled access subject terms.
Persons:
Riggio, Anita.
Subjects:
Illustrated children's books.
Document Types:
Correspondence.; Notebooks.; Publications.; Photographs.; Artwork.; Fliers. [printed matter]; Illustrations.; Manuscripts.; Galley proofs.; Typescripts.; Photocopies.; Notes.; Books.; Engravings.; Sketches.; Drawings.; Posters.; Newsletters.; Newspapers.
Occupations:
Illustrators.
Restrictions on Access
There are no access restrictions on this collection.
Acquisition Information
Bibliography
Author/illustrator
A moon in my teracup, Caroline House, Boyds Mills Press, 1993.
Beware the Brindlebeast, Boyds Mills, 1994. CLC C904
Gert and Frieda, Atheneum, 1990. CLC B84, Levy E2988
Noah Webster School 85: 1901-1986, Hartford, Connecticut, 1986.
Secret signs: along the Underground Railroad, Boyds Mills, 1997. CLC D778
Smack dab in the middle, Putnam's, 2002. CLC D776
Wake up, William!, Antheum, 1987. Levy B1165, CLC C44
Illustrator
The apartment house by Julie Madeline Schmidt, Abingdon Press, 1988.
Beethoven's cat by Elisabet McHugh, Atheneum, 1988.
Coal Mine Peaches by Michelle Dionetti, Orchard Books, 1991. Levy F1497
The Corey guide to postal exams by Richard J. Corey, Prentice Hall, 1988.
Dad Gummit & Ma Foot by Karen Waggoner, Orchard Books, 1990.
Favorite fairy tales told in Norway by Virginia Haviland, William Morrow, 1996.
Hobie Hanson, greatest hero of the mall by Jamie Gilson, Lothrop, Lee & Shepard Books, 1989.
I eat dinner by Margery Facklam, Little, Brown, 1987. CLC A4298
I go to sleep by Margery Facklam, LIttle, Brown, 1987.
Jumping Jenny by Bonnie Pryor, Morrow Junior Books, 1992. CLC B303
Noah's wife by Marty Figley, Eerdmans Books for Young Readers, 1998.
Whispering cloth by Pegi Dietz Shea, stitched by You Yang, Boyds Mills, 1995. CLC D472
Wiggie wins the west by Elisabet McHugh, Atheneum, 1989.
Detailed Description
- Series I: Children's Literature Illustration, undated, 1987-1994
  - Subseries A: Unpublished Work, undated, 1981-1986
  - Can you do now what Jenny learned how?, Burton Albert, undated
    - Rough cover art, watercolors (Box 7:, Folder 88)
  - Can you do now what Susie learned how?, Burton Albert, undated
    - Rough cover art, watercolors (Box 7:, Folder 89)
  - Can you do now what Tommy learned how?, Burton Albert, undated
    - Rough cover art, watercolors (Box 7:, Folder 90)
  - Can you do now what Willie learned how?, Burton Albert, undated
    - Artwork, gouache (Box 1:, Folder 1)
    - Collage (Box 7:, Folder 91)
    - Collage (Box 7:, Folder 92)
    - Cover art (Box 7:, Folder 93)
    - Cover art and illustration, color photocopy (Box 1:, Folder 2)
  - Cluck and Duck, undated
    - Original illustration, watercolor (Box 7:, Folder 94)
    - Illustrations, color photocopies (Box 1:, Folder 3)
    - Illustrations, photographic reproductions, (2 items) (Box 16:, Folder 177)
    - Matted illustrations, gouache, (2 items) (Box 9:, Folder 109)
  - I get cleaned up, Margery Facklam, undated
    - Story text (Box 1:, Folder 4)
    - List of suggested illustrations (Box 1:, Folder 4)
  - I like to play, Margery Facklam
    - Story text with note, 25 August 1986; (2 copies) (Box 1:, Folder 4)
  - My Word!, undated
    - Text samples (Box 1:, Folder 5)
    - Collages, photographic reproductions, (9 items) (Box 16:, Folder 178)
  - A Special family, 1981
    - Story text, (2 copies) (Box 1:, Folder 6)
    - Original art, matted, pen and ink (Box 1:, Folder 7)
    - Original art, matted, pen and ink (Box 1:, Folder 8)
    - Dummies, (4 items) (Box 1:, Folder 9)
    - Print of illustration on last page
  - Unpublished sample illustrations
    - The Lightey Stories, 1985-1986
      - Pencil illustrations, originals and photocopies (Box 7:, Folder 95)
    - Look toward the light, undated
      - Dummies (6 items: 3 miniature, 1 full-size complete, 2 incomplete) (Box 7:, Folder 196)
    - Robin Hill, undated
      - Pencil illustrations (Box 1:, Folder 10)
      - Pencil illustrations (Box 7:, Folder 196)
    - The Secret Seller, undated
      - Pencil sketches (Box 1:, Folder 10)
  - Subseries B: Published Work, undated, 1987-1994
  - The Apartment house, Julie Madeline Schmidt, 1988
    - Story text (Box 1:, Folder 11)
    - Preliminary sketches, photocopied (Box 1:, Folder 12)
    - Storyboard (Box 1:, Folder 12)
    - Final art, photographic reproduction, (2 items) (Box 16:, Folder 179)
    - Final line art, photocopied (Box 1:, Folder 12)
    - Sketches, pencil, original and photocopied (Box 8:, Folder 96)
    - Sketches, pencil (Box 9:, Folder 110)
    - Artwork, watercolor (Box 8:, Folder 97)
    - Artwork, watercolor, pp. 8-9 (3 versions), 10-13, 18-19, 20-21 (2 versions), 24-25, 30-31, (13 items) (Box 9:, Folder 111)
    - Original illustration, matted (Box 9:, Folder 112)
  - Beethoven's cat, Elisabet McHugh, 1988
    - Final artwork [page 13] (Box 1:, Folder 13)
    - Dustjacket (Box 1:, Folder 14)
  - Beware the Brindlebeast, 1994
    Older titles Birdie and the Bogey and Birdie and the Bogey Beast
    - Story text (Box 1:, Folder 15)
    - Early illustration, pastels and collage Birdie and the Bogey Beast (Box 12:, Folder 136)
    - Original dummies Birdie and the Bogey and Beware the Boogeybeast (Box 8:, Folder 188)
    - Photocopied dummy, Birdie and the Bogey (Box 8:, Folder 98)
  - Coal mine peaches, Michelle Dionetti, 1991
    - Artwork, color photocopies (Box 8:, Folder 99)
  - Dad Gummit & Ma Foot, Karen Waggoner, 1990
    - Research materials (Box 1:, Folder 16)
    - Sketches (Box 9:, Folder 113)
    - Final art, watercolor, pp. 1, 7-9, 12-15, 20-25, 30-31 (Box 9:, Folder 114)
      Includes jacket illustration and pp. 6-9, 12-15, 20-25, 30, 31
    - Black and white proofs with markings (Box 14:, Folder 155)
    - Dummy (Box 1:, Folder 17)
  - Favorite fairy tales told in Norway, Virginia Haviland, 1995
    - Final artwork, pen and ink, pp. 3, 16, 29, 33, 41, 47, 51, 53, 60, 65, 67, 71, 75, 79, 81, 85, 90, 20 items (Box 1:, Folder 18)
    - Cover illustrations, watercolors, (3 items) (Box 1:, Folder 18)
    - Line art test prints (Box 1:, Folder 19)
  - Gert & Frieda, 1990
    - Story text with markings (Box 1:, Folder 20)
    - Early artwork (Box 8:, Folder 100)
    - Storyboards and sketches (Box 8:, Folder 101)
    - Dummies, (2 items) (Box 1:, Folder 21)
    - Type samples (Box 1:, Folder 22)
    - Working illustrations, pencil sketches (Box 9:, Folder 115)
    - Original illustrations, gouache, cover, half-title, title page, 4-7, 12-13, 16-19, 22-23, 26-27, 31-32, (11 items) (Box 9:, Folder 116)
    - Galley 1 (Box 1:, Folder 23)
    - Text galleys, (2 items) (Box 8:, Folder 102)
    - Proofs, (2 items) (Box 8:, Folder 103)
    - Dustjacket proofs, (3 items) (Box 1:, Folder 24)
    - F & G, (2 items) (Box 1:, Folder 25)
  - Hobie Hanson, greatest hero of the mall, Jamie Gilson, 1989
    - Story text (Box 2:, Folder 26)
    - Sketches, pencil, original and photocopied (Box 2:, Folder 27)
    - Color photocopy of illustration (Box 8:, Folder 104)
    - Dustjacket (Box 2:, Folder 27)
    - Advertisment in Booklist, 1989 (Box 2:, Folder 27)
    - Advance readers copy (Box 2:, Folder 28)
  - I eat dinner, Margery Facklam, 1987
    - Story text (Box 2:, Folder 29)
    - Preliminary storyboard (Box 2:, Folder 29)
    - Book dummy (Box 2:, Folder 29)
    - Sketches, pencil (Box 8:, Folder 105)
    - Working and final artwork, pastel (Box 8:, Folder 105)
    - Final artwork, (2 items) (Box 2:, Folder 30)
    - Matted illustration (Box 8:, Folder 106)
    - Dummy (Box 2:, Folder 30)
  - I go to sleep, Margery Facklam, 1987
    - Correspondence, 1986 (Box 2:, Folder 31)
    - List of illustrations (Box 2:, Folder 31)
    - Preliminary storyboard (Box 2:, Folder 31)
    - Sketches, pencil (Box 2:, Folder 31)
    - Overlays (Box 2:, Folder 31)
    - Final artwork, (7 items) (Box 8:, Folder 107)
    - Book dummies, (3 items) (Box 2:, Folder 32)
  - Jumping Jenny, Bonnie Pryor, 1992
    Original title Glad Jenny
    - Original manuscript (Box 2:, Folder 33)
    - Story text with markings (Box 2:, Folder 34)
    - Original sketches, photocopied (Box 2:, Folder 35)
    - Original art, pen and ink (Box 2:, Folder 35)
    - Dustjacket sketches (Box 2:, Folder 36)
    - Dustjacket final art (Box 2:, Folder 36)
    - Dustjacket (Box 2:, Folder 36)
  - A Moon in my teacup, 1993
    - Proofs, 2nd printing (Box 9:, Folder 117)
      Autographed by Riggio with note "With warm wishes to Billie & the Northeast Collection of Children's Literature/Anita Riggio Nov. 8 1993"
    - Final artwork, oil on paper, (13 items) (Box 12:, Folder 137)
  - Smack dab in the middle, 2002
    Riggio worked through many styles before arriving at the one used for Smack dab in the middle. For each style she produced full sketches and dummies. The penultimate style progressed to final artwork.
    - Correspondence, 1999-2000 (Box 3:, Folder 37)
    - Text on paper and transparency (Box 3:, Folder 38)
    - Pencil sketches (Box 10:, Folder 118)
    - Preliminary artwork, early styles (Box 10:, Folder 119)
    - Pen and ink, penultimate style (Box 10:, Folder 120)
    - Pen and ink with text, penultimate style (Box 10:, Folder 121)
    - Collage pieces, penultimate style (Box 3:, Folder 39)
    - Dummies, penultimate style, (2 items) (Box 10:, Folder 122)
    - Dummies, (3 items) (Box 3:, Folder 40)
    - Dummies, (2 items) (Box 3:, Folder 41)
    - Dummy (Box 3:, Folder 42)
    - "Dummy #8" (Box 3:, Folder 43)
    - "Dummy #9", penultimate style (Box 3:, Folder 44)
    - Dummy, penultimate style (Box 3:, Folder 45)
    - "Dummy #10" and "Dummy #11," penultimate style (Box 10:, Folder 123)
    - Pen and ink collage pieces, backgrounds, penultimate and final styles (Box 13:, Folder 143)
    - Pen and ink collage pieces, backgrounds, penultimate and final styles (Box 13:, Folder 144)
    - Painting and printing accidents (Box 10:, Folder 124)
    - Painting and printing accidents (Box 11:, Folder 126)
    - Artwork in progress, color photocopies, penultimate style (Box 13:, Folder 145)
    - Final art, penultimate style (Box 10:, Folder 125)
    - Pen and ink, final style (Box 11:, Folder 127)
    - Pen and ink, final style (Box 11:, Folder 128)
    - Pen and ink, final style, one copy with text, (2 items) (Box 11:, Folder 129)
    - Final art, final style, pp. 1-3, 6-15, 18-27, 30-31, jacket back, (14 items) (Box 11:, Folder 130)
    - Final art, final style, (2 items) (Box 13:, Folder 146)
    - Materials for color selection and matching (Box 13:, Folder 147)
    - Paper sample (Box OS:, Folder 187)
    - Interior and jacket mechanicals, final style (Box 13:, Folder 148)
    - First proofs (Box 11:, Folder 131)
    - Second proofs (Box 11:, Folder 132)
    - Second proofs with markings (Box 11:, Folder 133)
    - Final printed pages, one-sided (Box 11:, Folder 134)
    - F & G (Box 13:, Folder 149)
    - Dustjacket first, second, and third proofs and final printing (Box 11:, Folder 135)
    - Artwork based on book, collage (Box 3:, Folder 46)
  - "This is my place," Gertrude Deutsch, 1990
    Cricket, Apr. 1990
    - 3 illustrations, watercolor, pp. 61, 61, 64 (Box 3:, Folder 47)
  - "Trapped by Time and Tide,", 1988 (Box 3:, Folder 192)
    Cricket, Sept. 1988
    - 8 illustrations, watercolor
  - Wake up, William!, 1987; Original titles "Mischievous Martin" and The Mischief that Martin Made
    - Early summary of "Mischievous Martin" (Box 4:, Folder 176)
    - Story text for "Mischievous Martin" (Box 4:, Folder 176)
    - Preliminary layout for "Mischievous Martin" (Box 4:, Folder 176)
    - Original wordless story art for "Mischievous Martin" pencil/gouache, (2 items) (Box 14:, Folder 150)
    - Working storyboard, (2 items) (Box 14:, Folder 151)
    - Cover overlay (Box 14:, Folder 152)
    - Original illustration, pencil/gouache, (1 item) (Box 4:, Folder 48)
    - Original art, half-title through p. 8, p. 10, (7 items) (Box 4:, Folder 49)
    - Original art, pp. 11-19, (6 items) (Box 4:, Folder 50)
    - Original art, pp. 20-32, (7 items) (Box 4:, Folder 51)
    - Photocopies of successive dummies, (8 items) (Box 4:, Folder 52)
      Includes loose pages of photocopied sketches
    - Original dummies, (5 items) (Box 4:, Folder 190)
    - Transparency (Box 14:, Folder 153)
    - F & G (Box 4:, Folder 189)
    - Unbound final print (Box 4:, Folder 189)
    - Dustjacket, (2 items) (Box 4:, Folder 53)
    - Misbound book, The entire first printing of the book was misbound. This is the only remaining copy and has been held out of the general collection so as not to be confusing. See CLC C44 or Levy B 1165 for correct copies. (Box 4:, Folder 191)
  - Wiggie wins the West, Elisabet McHugh, 1989
    - Story text (Box 5:, Folder 54)
    - Sketches (Box 5:, Folder 55)
    - 2 color drawings, jacket and unidentified drawing (Box 14:, Folder 154)
    - Final artwork, originals and photocopies, pp. 49, 65, 82, 103, 121, 125, 147, (7 items) (Box 5:, Folder 56)
    - Line art test prints, pp. 61 (2x), 117, (3 items) (Box 5:, Folder 56)
    - Galley proofs (Box 5:, Folder 56)
    - Dust jacket, (2 items) (Box 5:, Folder 57)
- Series II: Commercial Art and Graphic Design, undated, 1982-1989
  - American School for the Deaf, undated
    - Original art (Box 15:, Folder 164)
    - Poster, (2 items) (Box 15:, Folder 164)
  - Asylum Hill poster, undated (Box OS:, Folder 187)
  - "Cacophony,", undated; Prepared with the assistance of Debra Santini
    - Collage pieces (Box 5:, Folder 88)
    - Collage pieces (Box 15:, Folder 165)
    - Collage pieces (Box 14:, Folder 146)
    - Backgrounds (Box 12:, Folder 138)
    - Backgrounds (Box 14:, Folder 146)
    - "Cacophony" film
  - Cartoons, original sketches and photocopies, undated (Box 5:, Folder 59)
  - Commercial Christmas cards, undated
    - Artwork (Box 5:, Folder 60)
      Similar to eventual design for "PAX" card
    - Artwork, pen and ink (Box 14:, Folder 157)
    - Printed cards, (6 items) (Box 5:, Folder 61)
  - Connecticut Junior Republic Annual Report, 1989
    - Original artwork (Box 14:, Folder 158)
    - Transparency (Box 5:, Folder 62)
    - Printed cover, (4 items) (Box 15:, Folder 166)
  - "The Corey Guide to Postal Exams,", 1982 (Box 5:, Folder 63)
  - Courtroom illustrations (Box 12:, Folder 139)
  - "Dolores' Dilemma"[ Weekly Reader], undated
    - Story text with markings, (2 items) (Box 15:, Folder 167)
    - Photocopy of early sketch (Box 15:, Folder 167)
    - Final artwork with text, original and color photocopy, (2 items) (Box 15:, Folder 167)
  - Immanuel Congregational Church, undated
    - Bulletins (Box 5:, Folder 64)
  - "The Hill Center's Feast of Foods,", undated
    - Original artwork (Box 15:, Folder 169)
    - Printed volume (Box 5:, Folder 65)
  - "The Magic Cash Register,", 1984
    - Text with markings (Box 5:, Folder 66)
    - "The Store that Teaches,", 1982 (Box 5:, Folder 66)
    - Original artwork, (5 items) (Box 14:, Folder 159)
    - Photocopies of artwork (Box 14:, Folder 159)
    - Transparencies (Box 14:, Folder 159)
    - Dummies, (5 items) (Box 5:, Folder 66)
    - Draft cover, with markings, photocopies (Box 5:, Folder 66)
    - F & G (Box 5:, Folder 66)
    - Cover (Box 5:, Folder 66)
  - Newspaper illustration, 1982-1983
    - Red screen things, (12 items) (Box 5:, Folder 67)
    - Red screen things, (1 item) (Box 15:, Folder 170)
    - Original illustrations, pen and ink, pencil, (5 items) (Box 14:, Folder 160)
    - Clippings (Box 5:, Folder 68)
  - "The Pig,", undated
    - Photocopies of original illustration (Box 5:, Folder 69)
    - Photographic reproduction (Box 16:, Folder 180)
    - Photographic reproduction (Box 16:, Folder 181)
    - Slides, (2 items) (Box 16:, Folder 193)
    - Negatives, (3 items) (Box 16:, Folder 194)
  - Unidentified illustration project, undated (Box 15:, Folder 171)
  - Weekly Reader, 1991
    - Original art (Box 5:, Folder 71)
    - Newspaper clipping (Box 5:, Folder 71)
  - Unidentified commercial art, undated (Box 15:, Folder 172)
  - Unidentified commercial art, undated (Box 6:, Folder 72)
  - Unidentified commercial art, undated (Box 6:, Folder 73)
  - Unidentified commercial art, undated (Box 6:, Folder 74)
  - Unidentified commercial art, undated (Box 6:, Folder 75)
  - Unidentified commercial art, undated (Box 6:, Folder 76)
  - Unidentified commercial art, undated (Box 14:, Folder 157)
  - Unidentified commercial art, undated (Box 14:, Folder 161)
- Series III: Personal and Family Art, undated, 1968-2000
  - "Captain Shmock," photographs of sculpture, undated (Box 16:, Folder 182)
  - "The Christmas Elf,", undated (Box 15:, Folder 173)
  - "Dominoes,", 1968 (Box 6:, Folder 77)
    Lacordaire High School literary journal
  - Paintings, undated (Box Art storage)
  - Personal cards and announcements, undated
    - Original art, Christmas cards, undated (Box 6:, Folder 78)
    - Printed Christmas cards, undated (Box 6:, Folder 78)
    - Printed moving and birth announcements, undated (Box 6:, Folder 79)
    - New Year's card, 2000 (Box 14:, Folder 162)
      Based on early artwork from Smack dab in the middle
  - "The Velveteen Rabbit" photographic reproduction, undated (Box 16:, Folder 183)
  - High school art notebook, undated (Box 6:, Folder 80)
  - Sketch notebook, 1969 (Box 6:, Folder 81)
  - Sketch pad, 1978 (Box 6:, Folder 82)
  - Collages and photocopies from class with Leonard Everett Fisher, undated; (5 items) (Box 14:, Folder 163)
  - Unidentified personal art, undated (Box 6:, Folder 83)
  - Unidentified personal art, undated (Box 6:, Folder 84)
  - Unidentified personal art, undated; Includes art in response to 9/11 as part of a travelling exhibit sponsored by the Society of Illustrators (Box 15:, Folder 174)
  - Unidentified personal art, undated (Box 15:, Folder 175)
  - Unidentified personal art, undated (Box 12:, Folder 141)
  - Unidentified personal art, undated; Most of this artwork is from when Riggio was a high school student at Lacordaire Academy in Montclair, NJ. (Box 12:, Folder 142)
  - Unidentified photographs of art; research photographs, undated; (2 items) (Box 16:, Folder 184)
  - Unidentified photographs of art; research photographs, undated; (15 items) (Box 16:, Folder 185)
  - Unidentified photographs of art; research photographs, undated; (18 items) (Box 16:, Folder 186)
  - Unidentified negatives of art photographs, undated; (2 items) (Box 16:, Folder 195)
- Series IV: Ephemera, 1980-1996
  - Newspaper articles about Riggio, 1980-1988 (Box 6:, Folder 85)
  - School visit materials, 1996 (Box 6:, Folder 86)
  - Correspondence from children, 1996 (Box 6:, Folder 87)